Dede Badru

Tech Enthusiast & Developer Jl. Terusan Suryani, Bandung - 40222

dedebadru.com dede.badrujaman@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/dedebadru

OBJECTIVE

I am a web developer. I work for almost 4 years at different companies. My last position was the leader of frontend developer on Appschef (sister company of Walden Global Services) that was in charge to recruit the team member, manage the team, and manage the coordination with the clients.

EDUCATION

- Universitas Nurtanio Bandung Teknik Informatika
- SMK Negeri 11 Bandung Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak

RELATED EXPERIENCES

Developer, Weyland Indonesia Perkasa (2017 - Present)

Lead Frontend Developer, Appschef (2016 - 2017)

Lead Developer, Walden Global Services (2015 - 2016)

Developer, Walden Global Services (2013 - 2014)

RELATED SKILL

Programming language
Javascript framework
Database engine
Ruby on Rails, and Laravel
Jquery, and AngularJS
MySQL, and postgreSQL

• Subversion : Git

• Environments Dev : Vagrant, Docker

• Cloud : AWS, Google Cloud, and Digital Ocean

• Operating system : UNIX